Weiner is a documentary film directed by Josh Kriegman.
Documentary featuring a jaw-dropping, behind-the-scenes look at the attempted comeback of Anthony Weiner in
2013 as he mounts a campaign for New York City mayor in the wake of his sexting scandal.
Featuring unfettered access to the candidate and his campaign.
Self, played by Anthony Weiner.
Self, played by Huma Abedin.
Self - Senior Advisor, played by Amit Bagga.
Self, played by Adam S. Barta.
Self, played by Sydney Leathers.
Self, played by Jordan Zain Weiner.
Weiner is a 2016 American fly-on-the-wall political documentary film by Josh Kriegman and Elyse Steinberg
about Anthony Weiner's campaign for Mayor of New York City during the 2013 mayoral election.
The film explores themes of new york city, politics,
mayor, sex scandal, woman director.